<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jim&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jim&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>jamesfelps@gmail.com (Jim Felps)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jamesfelps@gmail.com (Jim Felps)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Frequently Do The Simpsons Repeat Couch Gags?</title>
      <link>/post/2020-08-17-simpsons/simpsons-couch-gag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jamesfelps@gmail.com (Jim Felps)</author>
      <guid>/post/2020-08-17-simpsons/simpsons-couch-gag/</guid>
      <description>While trying to figure out what content to include on this site, I decided it might be best to start re-creating visualizations found online. I looked through the subreddit /r/dataisbeautiful to find a visualization, and specifically one done in a language other than R, that I found appealing and the subject matter interesting. I look at this subreddit a few times each month and love the work that people post. I like that this subreddit contains visualizations from people that have been perfecting their craft for years and people just starting out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jamesfelps@gmail.com (Jim Felps)</author>
      <guid>/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>The picture above several weeks ago at Smithville Lake. Since the lockdown, one of my family’s biggest challenges has been to keep our kids active while also being safe. We don’t have a boat to get out on the lake, but through a friend we were able to find a secluded beach where we can bring some snacks, relax in a beach chair, and float on the lake for a few hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jamesfelps@gmail.com (Jim Felps)</author>
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently a financial analyst at Bluescope Buildings North America supporting the enigneering and sales teams by preparing monthly and ad hoc analysis by delivering necessary reporting to guide strategy decisions. I spent the past year designing and implementing a sales and operations planning group and currently lead the bi-monthly meeting with a cross-functional team of business leaders with the purpose of connecting the sales team with production leaders to algin demand capacity with market indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>